{
    "id": "e5ff3b23bcf34f4db76414169d884926",
    "title": "Verbs Complementation Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4ad4d4956a0e445c97cb91148224cd0a",
            "title": "Verbs Complementation Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why are you ………………… me like that?",
                    "description": "The verb look needs a preposition before its object.",
                    "answers": [
                        "looking",
                        "look at",
                        "looking at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like you to ..................... this story.",
                    "description": "The verb listen needs the preposition to before its object.",
                    "answers": [
                        "listen",
                        "listen to",
                        "hear to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s ………………. your plans.",
                    "description": "The verb talk requires a preposition before its object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "talk",
                        "talk about",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s …………………. your plans.",
                    "description": "The verb discuss does not take a preposition before its object.",
                    "answers": [
                        "discuss",
                        "discuss about",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………….. the station last night.",
                    "description": "Usually a preposition is necessary before an expression of place.",
                    "answers": [
                        "arrived",
                        "arrived at",
                        "arrived on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I enjoy …………………. cards.",
                    "description": "The verb enjoy is followed by a noun or an ing form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "playing",
                        "to play",
                        "to playing",
                        "play"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I suggest …………………. an attorney.",
                    "description": "The verb suggest cannot be followed by a to-infinitive.",
                    "answers": [
                        "you to consult",
                        "that you consult",
                        "to consult",
                        "that you to consult"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The police believe ………………… to be dangerous.",
                    "description": "A pronoun used as the object should be in its object form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "him"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like you to explain .......................",
                    "description": "The verb explain cannot be used with the structure indirect object + direct object.",
                    "answers": [
                        "us your decision",
                        "your decision to us",
                        "your decision us"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you suggest …………………?",
                    "description": "The verb suggest cannot be used with the structure indirect object + direct object.",
                    "answers": [
                        "me a good cardiologist",
                        "a good cardiologist to me"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please describe …………………",
                    "description": "The verb describe cannot be used with the structure indirect object + direct object.",
                    "answers": [
                        "us your new job",
                        "your new job us",
                        "your new job to us"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He fell ………………….",
                    "description": "Fell off is an inseparable phrasal verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "the ladder off",
                        "off the ladder"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}